Guide to the CONSOL Energy, Inc. Mine Maps and Records, 1857-2010 AIS.1991.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Survey Books, 1880s-1990s; XVI.
  - Mines, A-Z, 1.
    - Renton Mine book no. 24, inside levels; Renton Mine book no. 24, miscellaneous book (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Renton Mine book no. 25 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Renton Mine book no. 25, inside levels (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Renton Mine book no. 25, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine book no. 26 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Renton Mine book no. 26, inside transit; Renton Mine book no. 26, miscellaneous book (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Renton Mine book no. 27, no. 28; Renton Mine book no. 27 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Renton Mine book no. 27, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine book no. 28 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Renton Mine book no. 28, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine book no. 29 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Renton Mine book no. 29, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine book no. 29, transit book (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Renton Mine book no. 30; Renton Mine book no. 30, miscellaneous book (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Renton Mine book no. 31, transit book; Renton Mine book no. 34 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Renton Mine book no. 36, 37 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Renton Mine book no. 38, 39 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Renton Mine book no. 40, 41 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Renton Mine book no. 42, 43 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Renton Mine book no. 44; Renton Mine book A (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Renton Mine book A, B (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Renton Mine book B, C (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Renton Mine book C, D (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Renton Mine, accident surveys (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Renton Mine, electric power distribution; Renton Mine, gas wells (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Renton Mine, gas wells no. 2, 3 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Renton Mine, miscellaneous level book; Renton Mine, property owners (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Renton Mine, roof falls (non-accident); Renton Mine, shaft (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Renton Mine, town book; Renton Mine, triangulation (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Renton Mine, triangulation; Renton Mine # 1, book no. 1, miscellaneous book (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Renton Mine # 2, Renton Mine # 3, book no. 1 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 1, duplicate; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 1, entry book (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 1, level book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 1, mine circuit book (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 1, reconstruction book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 1, triangulation book (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 1A, triangulation book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 2, duplicate (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 2, entry book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 2, farm surveys (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 2, level book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 2, mine circuit book (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 2, reconstruction book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 3, duplicate (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 3, entry book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 3, level book (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 3, mine circuit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 3, miscellaneous book (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 4; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 4, duplicate (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 4, entry book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 4, level book (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 4, mine circuit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 4, miscellaneous book (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 4, transit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 5 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 5, level book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 5, miscellaneous book (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 5, outside level book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 5, transit book (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 5, transit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 6, level book (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 6, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 6A, transit book (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 6B, transit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 6C, transit book (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 7 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 7, level book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 7, transit book (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 8, level book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 8, miscellaneous book (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 8, transit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 9, level book (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 9, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 9, transit book (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 10; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 10, level book (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 10, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 10, transit book (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 11, level book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 11, miscellaneous book (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 11, transit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 12 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 12, level book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 12, miscellaneous book (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 12, transit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 13 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 13, miscellaneous notes; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 13, transit book (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 14; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 14, miscellaneous book (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 14, transit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 15, miscellaneous book (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 15, transit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 16, miscellaneous book (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 16, transit book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 17, miscellaneous book (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 18, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 19, miscellaneous book (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 20, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 21 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Renton Mine # 3, book no. 21, miscellaneous book; Renton Mine # 3, book no. 22 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Renton Mine # 3, room book no. 1; Renton Mine # 3, room book no. 2 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Renton Mine # 3, room book no. 3; Renton Mine # 3, room book no. 4 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Renton Mine # 3, room book no. 5; Renton Mine # 3, room book no. 6 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Renton Mine # 3, room book no. 7; Renton Mine # 4 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Renton Mine # 5, room book no. 7; Renton Mine # 5, room book no. 8 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Renton Mine # 6, book no. 30; Renton Mine # 6, book no. 31 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Renton Mine # 6, book no. 32; Renton Mine # 6, book no. 33 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Renton Mine # 6, book no. 35 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Renton Mine # 6, portions of miscellaneous books No. 2, No. 3, Newfield Mine (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Renton Mine # 6, miscellaneous book no. 1; Outside level book 2, 4, 5; Harmar Coal Co. (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Renton Mine # 6, field book no. 30, no. 32, no. 34; Harmar Coal Co. (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Ridgeway-Bishop Mine book no. 51; Ridgeway-Bishop Mine book no. 416, levels (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Ridgeway-Bishop Mine book no. 1043; Risher Mine book no. 675, outside notes (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Risher Mine book no. 675, outside transit notes; Six Mile Ferry, Risher Mine book no. 713, outside notes (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Risher Mine book no. 1166; Risher Mine book no. 1241, levels (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Risher Mine, Robbins Mine book no. 11 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4107 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4108 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4116 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4117 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4120 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4121 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4127 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4128 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4134 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4135 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4138 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4139 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4140 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4141 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4150 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4218 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Russell Stripping Operation book no. 4219; Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4149 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4149, 4153 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4153, 4154 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4154, 4155 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4155, 4157 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4157, 4164 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4164, 4165 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4165, 4176 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4177 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4178 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4197 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, book no. 4303, 4307 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 1, overburden on first cuts; Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4151 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4151, 4152 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4158, 4159 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4159, 4160 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4160, 4166 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4166, 4167 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4166, 4167 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4180, 4181 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4181, 4192 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4181, 4192 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4194 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4195 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4196 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4300, 4305 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Russell Stripping Operation # 2, book no. 4311, 4313 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Sandy Creek Mine book no. 1101; Sandy Creek Mine, levels (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Sandy Creek Mine, 2 unnumbered books (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Sandy McLean Mine book no. 1565; Sarah Mine book no. 178 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Sarah Mine book no. 1034, levels; Sarah Mine book no. 1106 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Saw Mill Run Mine book no.1551, South Hills Coal Co.; Shaner Mine book no. 107 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Shaner Mine book no. 249, levels; Shaner Mine book no. 477 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Shaner Mine book no. 249, levels; Shaner Mine book no. 477 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Shaw Mine book no. 259; Shaw Mine book no. 364, room book (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Shaw Mine book no. 365, Shaw Mine book no. 366, levels (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Shaw Mine book no. 386, miscellaneous notes; Shaw Mine book no. 1036 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Shaw Mine book no. 1127, Slope Mine book no. 49 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Smock Mine book no. 97; Smock Mine book no. 187, levels (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Smock Mine, Snowden Mine # 3 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Snowden Mine, Solar Mine book no. 1659 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Somers Mine book no. 1362, country mines, Somers Mine book no. 1516 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Somers Mine book no. 1518, room notes; Somers Mine book no. 1548; Country Mines, Division No. 7; Miscellaneous Mines (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Somers Mine book no.1674, general inside notes; Somers Mine book no. 1711 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Somers Mine # 1, book no. 62; Somers Mine # 1, # 2, # 3, # 4, book no. 139 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Somers Mine # 1, # 4, book no. 244; Somers Mine # 1, book no. 1045 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Somers Mine # 2, book no. 61, 179 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Somers Mine # 2, book no. 440, 473 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Somers Mine # 2, book no. 1014, levels; Somers Mine # 2, book no. 1410 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Somers Mine # 2, book no. 1411, level notes; Somers Mine # 2, book no. 1522, A. L. Brautegan Lease (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Somers Mine # 4, book no. 459, levels; Somers Mine # 4, book no. 1123 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Somers Mine # 4, book no. 1136, transit and room book; Somers Mine # 4, book no. 1316, room book (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Somers Mine # 4, book no. 1395, room book; Somers Mine # 4, book no. 1426, level notes (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Somers Mine # 4, book no. 1467, room and transit notes; Somers Mine # 4, book no. 1481, outside and inside notes (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - South Hill Mine book no.1611; Southwest Mine book no. 250, levels; Ocean Mine # 4 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Summer Hill Mine # 4; Summer Hill Mine book no. 344, room book (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Summer Hill Mine book no. 1142, 1358 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Sunnyside Mine book no. 1203, room notes, Sunnyside Mine book no. 1209 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Sunnyside Mine book no. 1230; Sunnyside Mine book no. 1331, room book (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Sunnyside Mine book no. 1432, Sygan Mine book no. 59 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Tremont Mine book no. 1202, 1229 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Tremont Mine # 1295, room notes; Umpire Mine book no. 1224 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Union Mine book no. 362, levels; Vesta Mine book no. 734, miscellaneous volume: profile and cross-sections (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 857; Lot plan, McDonald and Bigler, Book A; Vesta Mine book no. 858; Lot plan, McDonald and Bigler, Book B (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 861; Lot plan, McDonald and Bigler, Book C; Vesta Mine book no. 862; Lot plan, McDonald and Bigler, Book D (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 869, 870, outside (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 871, 872, outside (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 873, 875, outside (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 876, Weaver Strip Operation; Vesta Mine book no. 877, outside (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 879, 880, outside (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 882, 885, outside (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 887, 892, outside (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Vesta Mine book no. 893, slope work; Vesta Mine # 1, book no. 1, inside; Stations 1 to 129, July 1902 – May 1903 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Vesta Mine # 1, book no. 2; Stations 130 to 200, May 1903 – Feb. 1904; Vesta Mine # 1, book no. 3; Stations 200 to 415, Feb. 1904 – Aug. 1905 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Vesta Mine # 1, book no. 4; Stations 416 to 760, Aug. 1905 – Oct. 1908; Vesta Mine # 1, book no. 5; Stations 761 to 1350, Oct. 1908 – June 1915 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Vesta Mine # 1, book no. 729, 733 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Vesta Mine # 1, book no. 822; Outside book no. 31; Vesta Mine # 1, inside; Mellon Coal # 6; Stations 1 to 378, April 1917 – April 1923 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Vesta Mine # 1, levels; Mellon Coal 7; Vesta Mine # 1, room book 1, April 1917 – Sept. 1918 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Vesta Mine # 1, room book 2, Oct. 1918 – Sept. 1919; Vesta Mine # 1, room book 3 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Vesta Mine # 1, room book 104, Feb. 1904 – July 1904; Vesta Mine # 1, room book 105 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Vesta Mine # 1, room book 106, Dec. 1905 – Apr. 1909; Vesta Mine # 1, room book 110, May 1909-? (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Mine # 2, book 730, 732 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Vesta Mine # 3, book no. 51, Aug. 1902 – Dec. 1904; Vesta Mine # 3, book no. 52, Dec. 1904 – Dec. 1910 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Vesta Mine # 3, book no. 53, Dec. 1910 – Oct. 1915; Vesta Mine # 3, room book (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Vesta Mine # 3; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 61, 1904 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 62, 1904 – 1906; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 63, 1906 – 1907 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 64, Sept. 1907 – May 1909; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 67, 1909 – 1910 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 72, 1911 – 1912; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 73, 1911 – 1913 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 78, March 1913; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 81, Aug. 1913 – June 1914 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 101, Aug. 23, 1902 – Dec. 23, 1903, Station 0 – 334; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 102, Dec. 1903 – Aug. 1904, Station 334 – 696 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 103, Aug. 1904 – April 1905; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 104, April 1905 – Jan. 1906 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 105, Jan. 1906 – Jan. 1907; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 106, Feb. 1907 – Aug. 1908 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 107, Aug. 1908 – Oct. 1912; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 108 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 109, June 1914 – Dec. 1917; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 110 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 111, Oct. 1905 – Dec. 1907; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 112, Dec. 1907 – Jan. 1909 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 113, Jan. 1909 – Nov. 1909; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 114, Nov. 1909 – July 1910 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 115, July 1910 – Feb. 1911; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 116, Feb. 1911 – Oct. 1911 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 117; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 118, June 1912 – April 1913 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 119, April 1913 – June 1914; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 120, June 1911 – June 1915 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 121, June 1915 – Aug. 1916; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 122, Aug. 1916 – Sept. 1916 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 123, Sept. 1916 – Mar. 1919; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 124, Mar. 1919 – Sept. 1920 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 125, Oct. 1920 – Oct. 1922; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 126, Oct. 1922 – Aug. 1923 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 127, 128 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 129, 130 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 131, 132 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 133, 134 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 135, 136 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 137, 138 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 139, 140 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 141, 142 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 143, 144 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 145, 146 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 147, 148 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 149, 150 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 151, 152 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 153, 154 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 155, 156 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 156 C (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 157, 158 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 159, 160 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 161, 162 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 163, 164 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 165, 166 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 167 C (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 168, 169 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 170, 171 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 172, 173 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 174 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 175 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 176, inside notes (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 177 C (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 178 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 179, sketch notes (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 180 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 181 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 182, station book (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 183 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 184, sketch notes (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 185 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 186 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 187 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 188, 189 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 188, 189 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 191 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 201, Nov. 1903 – July 1905; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 202, July 1905 – Jan. 1909 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 203, Jan. 1909 – Aug. 1911; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 204, Aug. 1911 – Dec. 1915 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 205, Dec. 1915 – Nov. 1919; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 206, Nov. 1919 – April 1924 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 207, 208, inside level book (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 209, 210, level book (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 211; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 212, levels (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 213, levels (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 214, levels (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 215, levels (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 216, inside levels (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 217, inside levels (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 218, levels (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 219, inside levels (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 220, inside levels (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 221, inside levels (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 222, levels (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 223, levels (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 224, levels (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 225, water elevations, daily readings; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 226, levels (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 227, levels (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 228, levels (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 618, room book 1909 – 1911, 4th Hill; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 720 A, Picking and Screening, Plant 1944 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 816, 817, outside (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 818, 823, outside (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 824, 825, outside (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 832, 833, outside (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 834, 836, outside (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 839, 842, outside (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 843, 848, outside (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 849, 855, outside (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 856, outside (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 865, outside; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 868, outside book and test, D.D. holes (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 1205, fan test; Vesta Mine # 4, book no. 1206, ventilation survey, Richeyville Fan (Box 75, Folder 6)